I'm sorry.
Where's the train station?
The station?
Walk along this road
A third trust with a song on the left
Please.
The third trust is on the left.
Yes.
You can see the station on the right.
Is there a kaffi around here?
Yes, I do.
A sta - ba - cu - k, next to Ko - ni
I do.
Oh, my God.
It's right next to Kombini.
Yes.
It's a two-minute walk.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to go to the shrine of Yasaka.
Oh, my God.
If it's the shrine of Yasaka,
Walk along this road
Right at the end of the line.
To the right of the ticket.
Yes.
When you climb up the hill, you do it.
I'm sorry.
Is there a depat around here?
Yes.
There is a large depat in
front of the train station
Hey.
It's in front of the station.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Where's the vass stop for the airport?
Take this route and go!
It's on the right side.
A blue plate is the mark.
It's a blue plate, isn't it?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
How am I supposed to do
it on Golden Palace Island?
I'm going to go to Golden
Island with this basu.
From here on, it's Vasu, isn't it?
Yes.
It's 20 minutes long.
The fare is $2.00.
I'm sorry.
Where's the harle?
Oh, my God.
It'll be five minutes from here.
How am I supposed to do that?
Walk along this road
If the music is on your
right, you can see it.
I'm sorry.
Where is the entrance of the iron below?
If you go left here,
you will find the floor.
Please drop it down.
You're going to drop
the floor, aren't you?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Is there a Kombini near here?
Yes, I do.
Crossing the word "trust " is the left.
Crossing the word "trust" to the left.
Yes.
A plate of Sebu - i - bung
I'm sorry.
How Can I Get to the Courtyard?
Walk along this road
It's said to cross the bridge.
You're going to cross
the bridge, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm going to do it. "
You can see the big trees.